3ds.guide 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy - 3DS Hacks Guide

### Cookies

This site utilizes cookies in order to facilitate routing users through the guide instructions. Cookies allow for the sidebar of the page to display current progress through the site to help users navigate the instructions more easily.

### Embedded Content From Other Websites

This site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves as if the user has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics to monitor and analyze traffic. This site is hosted by Github Pages, which may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with this site. For more information about Github Pages as it relates to user privacy, see the [GitHub Privacy Statement](https://help.github.com/en/articles/github-privacy-statement).

### Information Collected

This site does not collect personal information. This site may collect usage information in order to analyze interest in content and to provide advertisers with information on an aggregate basis. No personally identifiable information is shared with third-party advertising companies.

Google (as a third party advertisement vendor) uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google allows them to serve advertisements to visitors based on their visits to this site as well as other sites. To opt-out of DART cookies, see the [Google Advertising Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Other third-party advertising servers or networks may also use cookies to track user activity on this site to measure advertising effectiveness or for other reasons provided in their privacy policies. This site has no access or control over any cookies which may be used by third-party advertisers.

### Third-Party Websites

This site may link to other sites for users to use or reference. This site is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. Users should be aware that the privacy policies of other websites may differ from this one.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

The contents of this Privacy Policy may be altered at any time and for any reason. For questions regarding this site’s Privacy policy, contact [plailect@gmail.com](mailto:plailect@gmail.com).
